#### Contact

bycomiller@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/corina-miller-b4b5a7a3 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Critical Care ICU CCU

Certifications
CCRN

# Corina Miller

RN, BSN, CCRN Oregon City, Oregon

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Acute Care, CCU, Nursing, Inpatient Care, and Critical Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Oregon Health and Science University.

# Experience

Providence Health & Services
Critical Care RN
August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Portland, Oregon Area

Kaiser Permanente RN, CVICU May 2012 - August 2018 (6 years 4 months) Clackamas, OR

Adventist Medical Center - Portland RN CVICU November 2010 - May 2012 (1 year 7 months)

Medical Staffing Network
Travel RN
September 2007 - October 2010 (3 years 2 months)
OHSU, Salem hospital

CMICU, Neuro trauma ICU, SICU/CVICU and Critical Care Float Pool contracts

Saint Alphonsus Health System Critical Care RN March 1999 - September 2007 (8 years 7 months)

Neuro trauma ICU, CCU, CVICU, ED, House Resourse RN Rapid Response.

Page 1 of 2

Providence Health & Services

9 years 8 months

RN diabetes renal unit

February 1991 - September 1999 (8 years 8 months)

Pediatric RN

February 1990 - March 1991 (1 year 2 months)

### Education

Oregon Health and Science University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1987 - 1990)

Portland State University

Pre-Nursing Studies · (1986 - 1987)